

# SELVANA **NAGUIB**

UI /UX Designer

**CONTACT ME** 

Email Address: Selvana.naguib4@gmail.com

Website: www.selvana-naguib.com

Mobile Number: 01211747667

Address: Sheraton Elmatar, Cairo, Egypt

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a multidisciplinary designer with a curious mind, I enjoy to meet new people and understand how they are solving problems, this is one of the reasons why I invest my time on meetups from product management to everything related to design (research, design thinking, design system, etc.) and talking to people in general, as always can be an opportunity to learn something new.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor**

2016

Computer Science and Information Systems, Helwan University

#### **School**

2012

Hafez Ibrahim Experimental Language School

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **UI / UX Designer at Arabian Systems (Emirates Auction)**

October 2020 - Present

#### Responsible for:

- Gathering and evaluating user requirements in collaboration with Business Analysts.
- Illustrate design ideas using storyboards, process flows and sitemaps.
- Develop UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and look like.
- Build the product style guidelines.
- Create original graphic designs (e.g. images, fonts, colors and animations) using Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD, Sketch, Figma, Principle.
- Identify and troubleshoot UX problems (e.g. responsiveness).
- Conduct layout adjustments based on user feedback.
- Upload the Designs on Zeplin for the developers to start implementing.

#### **UI / UX Designer at eBenefits Network**

July 2018 – September 2020

#### Responsible for:

- Wireframing and Designing Websites, Android and IOS Applications using Photoshop, Adobe XD, sketch, Figma & Balsamic tools.
- -Illustrating Company Logo, Banners and Brochures.

## **UI / UX Designer at Agile Technologies**

March 2017 - July 2018

#### Responsible for:

- Wireframing and Designing Websites, Android and IOS Applications using Photoshop, Illustrator, sketch & Balsamic tools.
- Implementing Designs using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap Languages.
- -Illustrating Company Logo, Banners and Brochures.

## **UI / UX Designer at Alexon Development**

June 2016 – March 2017

#### Responsible for:

- Wireframing and Designing Websites, Android, Windows Phone and IOS Applications using Photoshop tool.
- Implementing Designs using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap Languages.

## **SKILLS ME**

#### **Technical Skills**

#### **Personal Skills**

- Problem Solving:

- Adaptation:

- Representation:

- Team Working:

- Working under Stress:

- Attention to Details:

- Flexability:

- Willing to Learn:

- Hard Working:

# **LANGUAGES**

Arabic / English

## **INTERESTS**

Travelling / Acting / Drawing / Swimming

## **PROJECTS**

## **Arabian Systems (Emirates Auction)**

- Emirates Auction Website, Android & IOS Mobile Applications
- Command Center Website
- Almoqayem Website
- Emirates Road Assistance Android & IOS Mobile Applications
- Providal Portal Android & IOS Mobile Applications

#### **eBenefits Network**

- eBenefits Network Websites
- G&M Dashboard Website
- Quick Base Website
- Benefit Mall Website
- Idea Consult Website
- eBN Market Place
- No Code Mapping Tool
- SBA Loans Website
- Vive Website, Android & IOS Mobile Applications
- Felmie Website, Android & IOS Mobile Applications
- Logos, Brochures & Banners

#### **Agile Technologies**

- Kuwait Capital of Arab Youth Website & Mobile Applications
- ETender Website
- CMA (Contract System with Chatbot)
- Agile Portal Website & Mobile Applications
- Dry Clean Website, Dashboard & Mobile Applications
- Logos, Brochures & Banners

## **Alexon Development**

- eCommerce Website & Mobile Applications
- Saudi Post Mobile Applications

## **Freelance Projects**

- Payment Gateway Mobile Applications
- Tickets Mobile Applications
- Paysky Website
- Car Dealer Website
- D Writing Mobile Applications
- Chorus Mobile Applications

#### **Graduation Project**

- Health Care Cloud Computing

## **PORTFOLIO**

Please Check my Portfolio

http://www.selvana-naguib.com/#portfolio